let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Let f(x) = (x-2)(x-4)/x.",
        answer: "f(x): not a polynomial",
        options: [
          "f(x): polynomial",
          "f(x): equation",
          "f(x): not a polynomial",
          "f(x): a rational number"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 2,
        question: "The marks by students in a Math test are (Marks: No of students)=(0:3), (1:2),(2:3), (3:5), (4:x), (5:1). If the mode is 4 then the smallest possible value of x = ___",
        answer: "6",
        options: [
          "6",
          "4",
          "5",
          "2"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 3,
        question: "The marks by students in a Math test are (Marks: No of students)=(0:3), (1:2),(2:3), (3:5), (4:x), (5:1). If the mean is 2.25 then x = ___.",
        answer: "2",
        options: [
          "6",
          "4",
          "5",
          "2"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 4,
        question: "The length of the circumference of a circle equals the perimeter of a triangle of equal sides, and also the perimeter of a square. The areas covered by the circle, and the square are c, t and s, respectively then_____ ",
        answer: "c>s>t",
        options: [
          "s>t>c",
          "c>t>s",
          "c>s>t",
          "s>c>t"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Consider obtuse-angled triangles with sides 8 cm, 15 cm and x cm. If x is an integer, then how many such triangles exist ?",
        answer: "10",
        options: [
          "5",
          "21",
          "10",
          "15"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 6,
        question: "_____ is the irrational number lying between sqrt(2) and sqrt(3)",
        answer: "6^(1/4)",
        options: [
          "6^(1/4)",
          "2^(1/4)",
          "6^(1/2)",
          "2.5"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 7,
        question: "A rectangular kitchen table is 3 times as long as it is wide. If it was 3 m shorter and 3m wider, then it would be a square. What are the dimensions (in m) of the rectangular table ?",
        answer: "9 x 3",
        options: [
          "4 x 2",
          "16 x 4",
          "9 x 3",
          "12 x 6"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 8,
        question: "A right circular cone has radius 5 cm and height 8 cm. What is the lateral surface area of the cone ?",
        answer: "5pi x sqrt(89) sq. cm",
        options: [
          "40pi sq. cm",
          "445pi sq. cm",
          "5pi x sqrt(39) sq. cm",
          "5pi x sqrt(89) sq. cm"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 9,
        question: "A traffic signal board, indicating ‘BUMPER AHEAD’, is an equilateral triangle with side ‘b’. Find the area of the signal board. If its perimeter is 180 cm. ____ cm^2 will be the area of signal board?",
        answer: "900sqrt(3)",
        options: [
          "600sqrt(3)",
          "900sqrt(3)",
          "800sqrt(3)",
          "1000sqrt(3)"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 10,
        question: "The triangular side walls of a flyover have been used for advertisements. The sides of the walls are 122 m, 22 m and 120 m. The advertisements yield an earning of $ 5000 per m^2 per year. A company hired one of its walls for 3 months. How much rend did it pay ?",
        answer: "$ 16,500,000",
        options: [
          "$ 16,500,000",
          "$ 17,500,000",
          "$ 18,000,000",
          "$ 16,000,000"
        ]
      },

];